Hey.
Oh, my God, you cleaned.
Look at these floors.
You did the windows!
I have been begging you
for months and you did...
you cleaned.
And nagging works.
You know, uh...
I didn't actually do this.
Oh, no. Was I cleaning
in my sleep again?
No, it wasn't you.
Well, then, who?
I got a maid. Yay.
Oh, well, I hope by
"maid" you mean "mistress"
because if some other woman
was here cleaning, then...
Now, honey...
I know you don't like
to relinquish control.
Oh, relinquish is just
a fancy word for lose.
Look she's really nice, okay?
And she mentioned
that she adored
the way that you
arranged the sponges.
Did she really say that?
Yes, I distinctly remember
'cause I thought
it was a joke.
Now, just give her
a chance, okay?
Fine, I can do it.
( sighs )
What's the matter?
Well, usually when
I'm this anxious I clean.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
there for me, too. ♪
Whose cell phone is that?
It's so annoying.
Everywhere you go.
I think it's coming
from your bag.
I never get calls.
Hello?
Phoebe, hi, it's Eric...
from the Halloween party.
Ursula's fiancee.
Oh, my God. Eric, hi.
Wait, how did you
get this number?
I have a friend who's a cop
and he got it for me.
Wow, what an
incredible violation
and wonderful surprise.
Uh, listen, I just...
I thought you should know
I broke up with Ursula.
Oh, you did?
He did it. He did it.
Wow! What did he do?
Shh, I'm talking.
Anyway, I was wondering
if you were the sort of person
who eats lunch?
Are you asking me out?
Because it would be
kind of weird
since you just broke up
with my sister.
Yeah, um, okay.
I'm-I'm sorry. Bye.
No, wait, I was just saying that
so you'd think
I was a good person.
Fight for me.
Uh... I won't take no
for an answer.
Not great, but we can work on it
at lunch.
Okay, um, I can be
at your apartment in two hours.
Great. Uh... how do you know
where I live?
I've got friends, too.
Okay, Bye.
Bye.
Oh, my God.
I'm going out with Eric.
Ooh, this day
is really going to be
so much better than
I thought it was going to be.
Oh, Ross, I can't make lunch.
So, apparently
I'm available for lunch.
I can't, I'm busy.
I'm apartment hunting.
You're moving?
Yeah. I can't live with Joey
once the baby comes.
I don't want my child's first
words to be
( childlike ):
"How you doin'?"
So, does Joey
know you're moving?
Well, I haven't discussed it
with him yet
but I know
he's going to be relieved.
Last week he brought
this girl over
and I started talking to her
about morning sickness
and then I should her pictures
from my pregnancy book.
That's not really porn.
Not so much.
Hey, you know what?
Wait, if you're looking
for a place
I just heard in the elevator
this morning
that a woman
in my building died.
Oh, my God.
Was she old?
Does she have a view?
Well, I don't know, but how
great would that be, huh?
You living in my building.
I could help take care
of the baby.
I could come over
whenever I want.
With your permission.
Wow, that really would be great.
Yeah.
Well, can we see it?
Oh, maybe we shouldn't.
I mean, if she just died
this morning, out of respect.
Yeah, no... no, you're right.
Shall we?
Yeah.
Yes?
Hi, I'm Ross Geller.
I live in the building.
And I'm Rachel,
an admirer of the building.
I-I heard about Mrs.
Verhoven passing away
and I'm so sorry
for your loss.
She didn't pass away.
What?
My mother's still alive.
Oh, thank God.
It looked like we were going
to lose her this morning
but she's a tough old bird.
Oh, yeah.
Are you close
with her?
Of course.
Uh, yeah, she and I would
talk all the time
in the laundry room.
You speak Dutch?
Zeer veererd een
vriend van mijn
moeder te ontmoeten.
You know, I would but
it's just too painful.
So, she's really not dead?
No. She's hanging in there.
Mmm...
Do you think you--
could you tell me
is she hanging in,
in a one bedroom or a two?
Mrs. Bing...
this tile cleaner is incredible.
Where did you get it?
Oh, well, um...
I make it myself.
It's two parts ammonia
and one part lemon juice.
The secret ingredient is...
You know what?
We just met.
Okay, uh, I'm going to get
the clothes
from the laundry room now
and when I come back
I'll clean behind
the refrigerator.
I love her.
I'll be back in a minute.
Okay.
( door closes )
See? I told you.
She stole my jeans.
What?
I have been looking
for them all week
and she is wearing them.
So, she stole your pants
and then she came back
and wore them in front of you?
Don't you see?
It's the perfect crime.
She must have been
planning this for years.
I will prove it
to you, okay?
About a week ago,
I was wearing those jeans
and it dropped
a pen in my lap
and it left an ink stain
on the crotch.
Now, when she comes back
I will find it
and show you that stain.
Honey, isn't it possible that
the company that sold the jeans
made more than just
the one pair?
I guess.
So, shouldn't we give her
the benefit of the doubt
before we go snooping around
her crotch?
Fine, I'm just glad I didn't
give her my secret ingredient.
Out of curiosity,
what is your secret ingredient?
Yeah...
( knocking on door )
Hi.
Come in.
I'm so glad you're here.
Yeah, me, too.
Not in the shaky, angry way
that you are though.
Sorry, I just saw Ursula.
I had to get
the engagement ring back.
Oh.
Just seeing her
brought it all back.
All the lies...
the way she used me.
I just... I get so angry
just looking at her...
...face.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, it's just
when I look at you
I see her.
And when I see her
I get a little bit angry.
Maybe this is too weird.
No, wait.
There's only a problem
when I look at you.
I got it. I got it.
No, don't tear
out your eyes!
I was just going
to take out my lenses.
Oh, yeah, try that.
So, is that better?
Not really.
You... you're blurry
but you still look like Ursula.
You're Blur-sula.
Okay, wait.
Maybe... if I, if I just
don't look at you
for a while.
See? It works.
I'm not angry at all anymore.
This is a great date.
Look, Eric, turn around.
Look, I like you
but it shouldn't be
this hard, you know?
This is our first date.
You know, first dates
are supposed to be about
excitement and electricity
and, ooh, he just
touched my hand.
Did he mean to
touch my hand?
And, you know,
first kisses, and...
second kisses.
Thanks for the
coffee, or, uh...
Bedankt voor de
koffie, Gunther.
( speaks Dutch )
Yeah, we're done.
Aisel.
Aisel?
Aisel... aisel...
Hey, Ross, listen
you want to go see that new
IMAX movie on tide pools?
Really?
No.
But I got Knicks tickets for
you, me and Chandler, huh?
Sweet.
Finish your coffee.
Let's go.
Okay, I just have to stop by
my place first.
To tape the game?
You do this every time, Ross.
You're not going to be on TV.
No, no, I have to see if this
apartment became available.
You're switching apartments?
It's not for me,
it's for Rachel.
Rachel has an apartment.
But when the baby comes
she's going to want to move.
She is?
Yeah.
You don't expect her to live
there with a baby, did you?
I guess I didn't really
think about it.
Aisel.
Hey, Gunther, you're an aisel.
And I have...
( speaks Dutch )
Damn it.
Nice jeans.
Oh, thanks.
I like your top.
Oh.
( to herself ):
You're not getting it.
What happened?
Oh, I fell asleep.
I was thinking about
taking my lunch break.
Will you do
the top of the cabinets?
That would really work up
your appetite for lunch.
All right.
Hello.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, I've never had
a maid before.
Is this not okay?
Hey.
How was your game?
Uh, it was okay.
I... I ate way too much.
Oh.
Ooh.
So, um, I was
talking to Ross
and he said that you're
looking for a new place?
Oh, yeah.
Hopefully, across the street
if certain Dutch people
would just let go.
I was kind of
hoping you'd stay.
But, Joey, I have to go.
There's no room
for a baby here.
No room?
It's a baby.
It's, like, this big.
You know, I, uh...
y-y-you could...
You could put it over here...
or-or-or we could put it
right here.
Aw, it's cute, right?
Or-Or we could put it over here.
You wouldn't even notice it.
"Where's the baby?"
"Oh, it's right over..."
( chuckling )
Honey, it's not just a
matter of where you put it.
I mean, a baby
changes everything.
They cry all the time.
I mean, imagine
bringing home some girl
and trying to score
when there's a
screaming baby around.
I could use a challenge.
It's getting pretty easy.
Honey, it's so sweet
that you want me to stay
but I-I can't
do that to you.
I mean, it would disrupt
your entire life.
It's just... I...
I love living with you
so much.
You know, it's just
I wish things didn't have
to change.
I know.
You know,
I blame Ross for this.
I do, too, a little bit.
Yeah.
I'm going to miss you.
You're the hottest roommate
I ever hard.
Oh...
( moans softly )
Ooh.
Oh, no, I-I have to go.
Oh, I have a
massage appointment.
Oh, no, stay here.
We'll keep doing this.
I'll pay you.
No, I've gotten in
trouble for that before.
I'll see you later?
Absolutely.
Okay.
I love the way you kiss.
Really?
That's the thing I'm worst at.
You'll see.
Hey.
Hey, um, I think
Brenda needs a raise.
How come?
Because I put my head
between her legs.
Were you...
To see her pants?
They're my pants.
Are you sure?
Did you see the stain?
No, I was just
getting into position
and, then,
everything went dark.
Look, oh, my God, she is not
stealing from us, okay?
Will you let this go?
Fine.
( door closes )
She's wearing my bra.
Oh, dear God.
My pink flowered bra.
I recognize the strap.
And yet, you don't recognize
that you're crazy?
Here's the plan, okay?
I'm going to leave
and you're going to get a look
at Brenda's bra.
Here's another plan.
No.
I would do it
but she thinks
I'm attracted to her.
Why?
Did you not hear
where my head was?
Come on, come on,
we're a team.
We're in this together.
I fear a jury will
see it the same way.
Do this for me?
Come on, I catch you looking
at women's breasts all the time.
You see that?
Do you see this?
Uh...
All right, yes, okay,
I get your point
but if it's not her bra
will you just let
the woman clean
the apartment?
Yes, absolutely, okay?
Now, look,
you'll know it's mine
because on the right cup,
the lacy part
there's a very noticeable rip.
You need new clothes.
( knocking at door )
Hi.
How is she?
It's not looking good.
Oh! Oh... oh.
Yeah...
Well, I, uh...
I brought her some... bloemen.
That's so sweet.
Oh.
Would you like to come
in and say good-bye?
I'm sure it would
mean a lot to her.
Oh, I don't know
that it would.
( chuckles )
Well, her memory is
pretty much gone.
All right, then.
( mouthing )
Hey.
Welcome back.
Shall we pick up
from where we left off?
Oh, I don't know.
I'm still pretty tired out
from this afternoon.
Why?
Uh, the sex.
What sex?
Our sex.
We didn't have sex.
Well, if I didn't
have sex with you
I had sex with somebody that
looked an awful lot like...
Ew. Ew.
Oh, no.
Ew, ew, ew.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You-You...
You had sex with Ursula?
A-A little bit.
Sh-Sh... When she walked in
I thought she was you
and I kissed her and...
You didn't notice she was
wearing different clothes?
Well, I was just so excited
to see you.
Aw.
Ew, ew, ew!
Ugh!
You know what?
This is too weird.
No, no, it's not.
I don't want to lose you.
It's-It's like I was
saying to Ursula
when I was making
love to her and I
thought she was you...
No, it's too weird.
So, I guess this is it.
Yeah.
Well...
maybe it's for the best.
You smell just like her.
Yeah, so do you.
What are you doing?
I'm leaning.
This is where I lean.
Okay.
Brenda, a bee.
What?
Yes, it's flown into your blouse
and you better undo your buttons
lest it sting you.
I think I know
what's going on here.
You do?
Look, I know it must be hard
that your wife is a lesbian...
but it's wrong.
You're married.
I totally understand.
Good.
Could I just see your bra?
Hey.
Hi.
Where did you get
those jeans?
You gave them to me.
No, I didn't.
All right, I took them.
But I figured it would be okay
because you've got a big ink
stain on the crotch.
Oh, no.
Did you take my bra, too?
What bra?
The pink one
with the flowers.
You mean the one
that you're wearing?
I quit.
Sounds about right.
What is this?
Hey.
This is just
to give you an idea.
We can put screens here
so that the baby has privacy.
And maybe a mobile, you know,
over the crib.
And, uh... oh, look,
here's a baby monitor
which till the baby comes
we can use as walkie-talkies.
Right?
Oh, you're so sweet.
Oh, my God, and you
gave the baby Hugsie!
( laughs )
Uh...
That-That's really just to
show where the baby would go.
You know, why don't
I hold on to him
so there's no confusion.
But, Joey, the baby
is going to be crying.
It's going to be loud.
I'm loud.
It's going to be up all night.
I'm up all night.
It's going to poop.
Hello?
What about all the women
you want to bring home?
Look, if I'm bringing home
a woman
who can't stand
being around a baby
then maybe I don't
want to be with that woman.
Or maybe we'll just do it
in the bathroom of the club.
Joey, are you sure?
Yeah.
Look, I know sometimes
it'll be hard, okay?
But... it'll also be
really... really great.
Please, Rachel.
I really want you to stay.
I want me to stay, too.
Oh...
Thank you.
Joey, and look
at this crib.
It's so cute.
I know, I found it
on the street.
Are you...?
Really?
It's in such
good condition.
Yeah.
Wow.
Whoa, whoa, what's
under the cover?
I don't know.
It's moving.
Ooh.
It's still...
Oh, it's got a tail!
Get it out of here!
Okay!
Get it out
of here!
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Well...
The old lady died.
And how do I know?
Because her dying wish
was for one last kiss.
But I don't care
because you got the apartment.
Yes!
Ooh, yeah.
Um... I think I'm going
to stay here.
Isn't that great?
Wha...? Y...
( stammering )
Aisels!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]